<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Chronos Pointer - Schedule Menu Enhancement</name>
  <modVersion>1.5.0</modVersion>
  <author>CoolNether123, TreadTheDawnGames, ZManJim</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
    <li>1.6</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>CoolNether123.ChronosPointer</packageId>
  <description>Enhances the schedule panel with dynamic time indicators for improved colony management and time tracking.
  
Features:
- Hours Bar: A dedicated bar above the schedule's hour numbers, visually representing the day and night cycles.
- Dynamic Time Pointers:
    - Arrow Pointer: An arrow that moves in real-time above the schedule, precisely indicating the current hour and minute.
    - Hours Bar Time Cursor: A small vertical line within the "Hours Bar" that accurately traces the current time, dynamically changing color with the daylight level.
    - Full-Height Time Indicator: A vertical line spanning all pawns' schedules, moving in sync with the other pointers to show the current time for all colonists at once.
- Customizable Colors: Adjust colors for all indicators, cursors, and bar segments to match your visual preferences.
- Incident Interactions: The "Hours Bar" updates its colors and visual effects to reflect current map conditions like Solar Flares, Eclipses, Toxic Fallout, Volcanic Winter, and Auroras.
- Comprehensive Settings: All elements, including appearance, visibility, and behavior, are fully configurable through the settings menu.

This mod provides an intuitive and visually appealing way to track time in RimWorld, making it easier to manage colonist schedules and activities throughout the day and night cycle.
  
All features can be toggled and customized in the mod settings, allowing you to tailor the experience to your liking.

Any issues or have some ideas? Come by my discord at: https://discord.gg/QYBBaRkKWs
  </description>
  <url>https://github.com/coolnether123/chronosPointer</url>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
  <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
    <li>Mysterius.CustomSchedules</li>
  </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>
